[
    {
        "Topic": "harry potter",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "From which platform at Kings cross does the Hogwarts Express train depart",
        "correct_answer": "Nine and three quarters",
        "options": [
            "Gringotts",
            "Wand",
            "Nine and three quarters",
            "The trolls club"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Topic": "harry potter",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Harry has a scar on his forehead. Which shape is it?",
        "correct_answer": "lightning bolt",
        "options": [
            "pigs tail",
            "lightning bolt",
            "shaining star",
            "egg"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Topic": "harry potter",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Harrys uncle and aunt, the dursleys live at what address?",
        "correct_answer": "Number 4, Privet drive",
        "options": [
            "Nine and three quarters",
            "The trolls club",
            "Number 4, Privet drive",
            "Gringotts"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Topic": "harry potter",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Hermiones parents are not wizards. What non-wizards jobs do they do?",
        "correct_answer": "Mechanic",
        "options": [
            "Physician",
            "Tailor",
            "Dentists",
            "Mechanic"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Topic": "harry potter",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "how do the dursleys say that Harrys parents died?",
        "correct_answer": "car crash",
        "options": [
            "car crash",
            "aeroplane crash",
            "cancer",
            "heart attack"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Topic": "harry potter",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "how old was Voldemort when he opened the chamber of secrets?",
        "correct_answer": "16",
        "options": [
            "15",
            "17",
            "16",
            "18"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Topic": "harry potter",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "On a Quidditch pitch, how many goal posts are there in total?",
        "correct_answer": "4",
        "options": [
            "4",
            "6",
            "5",
            "7"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Topic": "harry potter",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In philosopher's stone, who reports the commentary for the quidditch matches at hogwarts",
        "correct_answer": "Lee Jordan",
        "options": [
            "Dumbledore",
            "Mrs Norris",
            "Lee Jordan",
            "Professor Sprout"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Topic": "harry potter",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "In second year, Hermione drank Polyjuice potion which gave her rat like features",
        "correct_answer": "false",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Topic": "harry potter",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In which year (1-7) did Harry go on his first date with cho chang?",
        "correct_answer": "5",
        "options": [
            "2",
            "3",
            "4",
            "5"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Topic": "harry potter",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Sirius Black was sorted into Slytherin house",
        "correct_answer": "false",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true"
        ]
    }
]